i feel like i do a lot of things wrong
uh
like ladies do you ever uh
you ever take a
screenshot of a text message and then
accidentally send it right back to that
person then oh no
oh you're busted
because we all know what a screenshot of
a text message means right it means i'm
talking trash about you on a group chat
that you're not a part of okay
and
they've got to see this
i've done that so many times i've
devised my own defense mechanism right
as soon as i see that i've shot that
screenshot off to the wrong person i
start to shame the recipient
trust me it works you can have this one
you just go
look what you said
i had to take a picture of it and send
it back to you so you could see how
ridiculous it looked coming through my
phone in my order yeah
i'm a really good friend for pointing
this out to you before anybody in that
group chat got a hold of it
uh i'm about texting i'm also bad at
instagram right do you guys remember
when instagram used to be just people
taking photos of their food and the rest
of us laughing at them behind their
backs
right
and now every instagram post is the same
it's just a girl in a bikini facing
backwards like family vacation with my
grandparents and i'm like ah
i miss lasagna
call me old-fashioned what i wouldn't
give for a good spaghetti pick right now
you know what i mean
when did it get to be all butts i don't
understand it's all butts
or like ladies when did we collectively
decide as a gender that when someone
gets pregnant they have to stand out
barefoot with a flower crown and an
evening gown in the middle of the woods
to take pictures for instagram
what are we doing
why are you wearing fairy wings helen
you work in hr you're not that friendly
did you meet your husband in the shire
what are we doing here
look i want to rent the runway too i get
it i just have a birthday party or
something
every photo is the same i know that
because i'm very fake on instagram i'm
trying to do all the poses
everything's so posed it reminds me of
senior photos
do you guys remember seeing your photos
when you would take a freshly graduated
18 year old kid
take them out for a photo go stand out
in front of the railroad tracks cross
your arms
that's the pose right there nothing says
i just graduated like someone crossing
their arms on a train track
i just graduated
i'm gonna stand on these train tracks
[Laughter]
it's a photographer it's a metaphor for
the train of life just getting ready to
run him over
here are some bills kid i
am
or it's like this
this ain't my truck
four years you knew me for four years in
high school didn't know i had a cowboy
hat did you
i waited four years to come out of the
closet as a cowboy here i am
seeing your photos
who wants a wallet size keep in touch
right same photos every single time
you